Contact

konstantin@rogozhkin.com

www.linkedin.com/in/konstantin-rogozhkin-8aa946132 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Управление ИТ-инфраструктурой Осуществление проектов Сетевое администрирование

Konstantin Rogozhkin

I am building bots using python and LLM.

Mar del Plata, Buenos Aires Province, Argentina

Summary

Konstantin Yurievich Rogozhkin

Specialist in Artificial Intelligence and Big Data

"Development of recommendation systems.

Development of chatbots for customer engagement.

Demand forecasting system development.

Text generation system development for job listings and resumes.

"Developed chatbots for companies like Leads, AlSales, and a pilot project with T2. Over 2 million unique users have interacted with my chatbot."

Over the last ten years, specialized in developing AI and Big Data solutions. Developed a chatbot for AISales, leveraging NLP and machine learning to automate sales and customer support. Created a demand forecasting system using time-series and regression analysis to optimize online store inventory.

"Russian Federation, Kirov

Federal State Budgetary Educational Institution of Higher Professional Education 'Vyatka State Humanitarian University'

DIPLOMA KV No. 64425

State Examination Commission, July 3, 2012 Konstantin Yurievich Rogozhkin

AWARDED THE QUALIFICATION

Informatics-Economist specializing in 'Applied Informatics (in Economics)'"

LLC AlSales (Technical Director)

Experience

Self-employed

NEIRA AI FOUNDER

January 2024 - Present (1 year 2 months)

AISales

Chief Technology Officer

August 2017 - February 2022 (4 years 7 months)

CallProfit

Директор по ИТ

January 2015 - 2017 (2 years)

Technical Director

Building the IT infrastructure of the project:

- 1) Website creation
- 2) Implementation of Bitrix24 CRM
- 3) Automation of business processes and Building IT infrastructure of the project.
- 4) Hiring and training of programmers/system administrators. Control of their work.
- 5) Integration of CRM call-center with external systems
- 6) Implementation of Oktell call-center system
- 7) Development of modules for Oktell system
- 8) Visualization of reports (Google DataStudio)
- 9) Hiring and training control programmers/system administrators
- 10) Organization of technical support for users

Creation and Implementation of analytics for the managers of KC:

Real-time dialer statistics

http://joxi.ru/aD2PJysp4PPar3.png

Statistics on operator conversion in real time

http://joxi.ru/4DmByRFw1aaLrP.png

Line statistics:

http://joxi.ru/jgmvnVfLJWoKma.png

(Dialing by lines, Calls by lines and by hours, Percentage of line utilization)

AviHost

Co-Founder

January 2007 - 2013 (6 years)

Кировская область, Россия

Co-founder of project

Writing and implementing a business plan;

Preparing the company for commercial launch;

Development of tariff offers and advertising support;

Consulting clients on the company's services (shared hosting, virtual servers, domain names, SSL certificates), ticket system, online chats;

Management of company finances;

Work with dealers and partners;

Development of website and internal systems;

Commercial launch of the company;

Promotion of websites in search engines;

Achievement of high-frequency search engine rankings in the TOP;

Optimization and maintenance of contextual advertising (Google AdWords,

Yandax Direct);

Drawing up TOR and CP for each project;

Reporting and task planning;

Provision and control of tasks for programmers and designers;

Education

Вятский Государственный Гуманитарный Университет ИНФОРМАТИК-ЭКОНОМИСТ по специальности «Прикладная информатика (в экономике)» · (September 2007 - July 2012)